One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
in the blank slates of our minds
Luffy,
hurry up and get over here!
We're Not in Hell
We're all set to depart anytime now!
Once Luffy gets back, we can set sail!
Okay.
Look, simply put, there are about
as many battleships as there are of us.
Even if we do set sail,
it's virtually impossible to get out of here.
This is a report from northwest of the main gate.
We have retrieved all
Enies Lobby's marines and officials.
Also, at the main gate,
we identified about fifty pirates—
including the giants—escaping the main island.
It's those guys!
That's Zambai and the others!
See! I told you! They escaped the island just fine!
I wasn't worried about them at all!
Really, they wouldn't die!
Not even if you killed them!
Just the other day–
We have completely eliminated them
with a barrage of cannon fire.
All are confirmed dead.
Under these circumstances,
it's impossible to survive on the main island.
Hence, the number of survivors
on Enies Lobby's main island is zero!
Reporting from Battleship 2.
The courthouse and the Tower of Justice
located in the southeast of the island,
as well as the underground passage
that leads to the bridge,
have all been destroyed.
The only target left is the Bridge of Hesitation.
Franky!
Those guys!
Alright, you guys go straight to the courthouse and meet up with Straw Hat-san.
We're gonna split into two groups
and bring down that drawbridge.
Galley-La's shipwrights, too?
When you see those guys, tell them,
"You're fired."
Oimo! Kashi!
How...
dare you...
deceive us?!
I guess Yokozuna was with them, too.
Do you wanna come along?
Sodom and Gomorrah, too! Everyone!
He says, "I'll be faithful
to Big Bro Franky for the rest of my life!"
That trench mortar hit him in the chest!
Get over here before he falls!
No one's getting saved
unless you guys keep moving!
How is it...
that people can die so easily?
You can't see people on a map.
They just erased a small island from the world map,
all without a shred of emotion.
That's what a buster call is!
Bro! We came to rescue you-waina!
Bro! Come home with us!
Hurry up, Straw Hat!
Your friends are here waiting for you!
Don't you dare die on us!
Franky!
Rubber Rubber...
Jet Pistol!
He jumped backwards to reduce the impact!
Finger Pistol!
Jet Bullet!
Twin Jet Pistol!
Rubber Rubber...
I'll show you...
my most potent technique,
one that pushes the Six Powers to their limit!
Six Powers Esoterica:
Six King Gun!
It's like... the impact dials from Sky Island,
but it's several times more powerful!
Tempest Kick: Victory Bird!
Luffy!
Lucci is powerful.
If Straw Hat hadn't held him back in there,
to be honest,
I don't know how many of us would've died.
You know, sometimes I feel...
Luffy always knows from the start
the person he has to fight.
I'm definitely gonna beat up that pigeon guy.
He just has animal instincts...
even better than your own.
I have a report, sir!
Straw Hat Luffy is in the first column!
So he's alive?
Tell all ships to take position
around the Bridge of Hesitation!
– Yes, sir!
– Let's go! Hurry up!
He won't... die, right?
Are you an idiot?
What'd you say?!
Only an idiot calls others idiots!
What's going on?
The wall?
The first column is now cut off!
They destroyed half the bridge!
Why'd they do that?!
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 and Straw Hat Luffy
are in the first column!
The battleships are coming this way!
All ships, take position around the Bridge of Hesitation!
On both the bridge and escort ship,
we have identified nine pirates,
including Pirate Hunter Zoro and Nico Robin!
It appears that they're the main culprits
who defeated CP9 in the Tower of Justice!
They'll recapture Robin!
We're not gonna let them!
At any rate, they're fierce.
The legendary Enies Lobby
has stood impregnable for 800 years,
all because CP9 has watched over it
for many generations.
And yet, a single group of pirates defeated CP9,
and their captain can contend
with Mr. Rob Lucci, of all people.
It seems that Straw Hat Luffy is no mere rookie.
But he can't defeat Mr. Lucci.
And we will clearly annihilate his crew here.
This is the end of the road for these villains.
Hey, look over there!
Luffy-kun!
We're here!
We all got to the bridge, safe and sound!
We're okay!
You don't have to worry about us, Luffy-kun!
We rescued Robin-chan, too!
All that's left is for you to beat him!
Take him down, Luffy!
We'll all make it through this...
and leave this place!
Now it's just a matter of how long
we can hold them off.
It's as you said, your friends are all still alive.
Incredible.
But we'll see if you still have
that look on your face a few minutes from now.
Evil cannot be allowed to thrive in this world!
Stand down if ranked lieutenant commander or below!
As for the 200 elite captains and commanders, eliminate the enemy on the double!
C-Captains from Headquarters?!
They're in the same class as that Smoker freak!
We're taking on that many guys at that level?!
That's proof they're scared of us.
Grandma, I'm scared.
Hm? Where's Sanji?
He was here just a moment ago.
What? Where'd that idiot cook go at a time like this?
All hands prepare for battle! Move out!
Yeah!
Talk is cheap; bring it on already!
Nice. I get to go wild one more time.
We'll draw the line here
and give it everything we've got!
Hold your ground until Luffy gets back,
no matter the cost!
We have to get off the ship! If it's damaged,
we'll lose our chance to escape!
They will never catch me again!
I can't move!
Attack!
Recover Nico Robin!
We can't let them take her back after having come so far!
Two hundred elites from Navy Headquarters?
Fine by me!
But there are so many of them!
Weapons...
Left!
Only dealing with one or two at a time is such a hassle. Attack me all at once!
Feel the power of Sogeking!
Sunflower Star!
So you're looking for a fight
using guns and cannons?!
Take this!
That doesn't work on me!
Weapons Left!
You're not getting away from me!
Strong Right!
Grandma, the Navy's on its way!
That's not good.
Robin, stay here. I'll hold them back!
Here I come!
Thunder Charge:
Swing Arm!
Thunder Ball!
– What's this?!
– Clouds?!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
I did it!
You think you can fight us
with that joke of a weapon?!
You pirate bitch!
Robin!
I'm part of the Straw Hats, too.
When we fight, let's do so together.
There's more?!
Hey there! We're hostages!
We're weak!
Stay strong until Luffy gets here!
Shave!
What's the matter?
It seems that doping technique of yours is losing its edge.
Your struggle means nothing!
Enies Lobby is your last stop after all!
That's just reality!
Rubber Rubber Jet Axe!
I don't care if this island is destroyed in the process.
That woman is a threat
to the World Government's agenda.
I will pursue her to the ends
of the earth to eliminate her...
in the name of dark justice!
We came here to take Robin away from all that!
Jet Stamp!
Six King Gun!
Luffy!
– I got him!
– Watch out!
Hey! Now's not the time
to be spacing out, Soge–
Luffy!
What're you doing?!
Get up!
Luffy!
Weapons Left!
Super!
Commander!
What's with those pirates?!
This is insane!
They're holding their own against captains!
Does that woman have powers?!
I'll take care of her. Stay back!
Cien Fleur:
Flip!
Here we go!
Thunder Ball!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
That'll do!
So I guess these guys aren't
your typical grunts, huh?
Two-Sword Style:
Hawk Surge!
Who's next?!
Usopp!
Luffy!
U-Usopp?
S-So... you came?
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
I'm here to rescue Robin!
I didn't come to see your face!
Damn, what an ass!
Hey, you! CP9's boss cat!
I'm talking to you!
Now it's my turn! Bring it on!
Th-That's right! I'm your opponent!
Hey!
Hey... don't! Don't! Hey!
Leave him alone!
You've already lost.
I have no business with you.
They're all gonna die anyway.
Just stay right there and watch.
All right, come on, boss cat!
I'm gonna blow you away!
Are you stupid?! Stop it, Usopp! He'll kill you!
Shut up! What can you do
when you're almost dead?!
He's mine! I'm gonna kick his ass!
Then get up already!
Stop looking like you're about to die!
It's not like you!
There may be nothing but smoke above us,
but we can still see the sky!
We can see the sea, too!
We're... We're not in hell!
Stop acting like you're about to die, you jerk!
Don't make us worry, dammit!
I know!
This isn't hell or anything close to it.
Luffy!
You have to beat him!
We're all going back together, Luffy!
You're damn right!
So you can still move?
I never said... I'm done.
Until I defeat you,
I won't... hit the floor again!
Vital Response: Terminate.
I've had enough of this farce.
My sheer power will crush you once and for all!
Don't worry about your friends, Straw Hat.
Since you wish to be together with them again,
I'll send them to join you in hell!
Spots!
Luffy!
Victory Bird!
Dammit! What's their deal?!
I can't hit them!
Hey! I won!
Take this!
Witness the power of the Berry Berry Fruit!
Dammit! I'm trapped!
There's nothing you can do!
Thanks!
Hey, you! Hold on a sec.
If you like flying so much...
Hey! D-Don't!
Weapons Left!
Careful! They've got ability users among them!
They could say the same about us!
Treinta Fleur: Clutch!
So you are Roronoa Zoro?
And if I am?
I will defeat you!
Fine!
I ate the Rust Rust Fruit and became a rust man.
You cannot defeat me.
Dammit! My Yubashiri!
I will turn those swords you cherish to rust.
How intriguing.
Let's give it a test.
Now you get it, right?
You cannot defeat me with swords!
I... I can't move my body!
I rusted your joint. I will continue
until your entire body is rusted over!
Dammit!
Firebird Star!
Are you okay, Zoro-kun?!
Rubber Rubber Jet Pistol!
I'm not gonna take another one of those!
Ultimate Whorl:
Six King Gun!
Until I defeat you,
I won't... hit the floor again!
You'll soon regret that you took in such a vexatious woman.
Rubber Rubber...
We're through. You'll never see me again.
This does not concern people like you.
Robin intends to die for us!
Iron Body!
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive...
after making the entire world your enemy!
I will pursue her to the ends
of the earth to eliminate her...
I want to live!
Jet...
Gatling!
What's going on?!
What happened?!
Luffy!
The first column!
H-Hey, what's that?
Hey! Look over there!
Th-This is a report to all ships.
This is a report to all ships!
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 was just...
was just defeated...
by the pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy!
It's over.
We'll be okay now.
We're gonna go back together!
Robin!